

Contact

- @ jgrancher@gmail.com
- **6** 0478 011 164
- Sydney

On the Internets

- g jerem.app
- □ jgrancher
- ☼ @jgrancher
- ំ្រា jgrancher

Last projects

- Create with Google
- Card Companion
- Audience Connect
- Succailure TV

Skills

- TS JS & TypeScript
- React & React Native
- SCSS & CSS-in-JS
- Node.js & GraphQL

Jeremy Grancher

Senior Front-End Developer

I am a senior web developer specialised in front-end who loves to craft beautiful digital products using Javascript technology such as React. I take special care for little details, following best practices, web standards and code hygiene.

Professional Experience

wstwo

Senior full-stack developer @ ustwo

2017 - Now Sydney

- Architecture, development and maintenance of the Create with Google website, using Python on the backend, and leveraring Jinja macros on the front-end to keep a component-based approach.
- Early prototyping and creation of the Audience Connect MacOS & Windows application for Google, enhancing Google Slides with offline videos and real-time interactions with the audience, using Electron, Preact, Firebase and Jest.
- Development of the Qantas loyalty platform "Card Companion" with React, Next.js, GraphQL and Apollo: cardcompanion.qantas.com
- Creation of component libraries and following best practices whenever possible, using Storybook, Emotion & Styled-System.
- Recurrent collaboration with designers to provide feedbacks, estimations and workarounds but also animations, often using a mix of SVG, CSS and JavaScript.

hŏl'ər

Senior front-end developer @ holler

2015 - 2017 Sydney • Creation of a series of websites for Audi Australia, including their main loyalty portal developed with React, React-Router and Redux: myaudi.com.au



2014 - 2015

Sydney

Front-end developer @ Redfox Media

- Development of WordPress websites for small to medium businesses.
- Creation of Wordpress themes and plugins in PHP, HTML5 and SCSS.

exomind

Front-end & iOS developer @ Exomind (IT Consulting company)

2012 - 2014 Paris

- Creation of a news mobile website for TF1 (France's first public TV channel): mytf1news.fr
- Development in collaboration with TBWA of the promotional mobile website for Invictus, Paco Rabanne's new fragrance, using GSAP animations: thefwa.com/cases/invictus-award-by-paco-rabanne

Education



Master in Digital Communication Engineering and Management



Diploma in Information Technology